http://www.usairnet.com/privacy-and-security/

your password
Forgot your password?
your email
A password will be e-mailed to you.
Overview
Air Sports Net aims to implement online resources in a safe, secure manner that values your privacy when visiting our website. This privacy statement discusses the gathering, use, disclosure, and protection of information obtained by Air Sports Net when you visit usairnet.com website.
Information Collected
Air Sports Net uses Google Analytics and other IP tracking methods to obtain knowledge about its website’s effectiveness. When users visit an Air Sports Net, the service may collect some or all of the following information:
The names of domains; for example, “xyzcompany.com”;
IP addresses, which are numbers automatically assigned to a computer when using the Internet;
The type of browser and operating system used to access the site;
The Internet address of the website from which users linked directly to the site;
The search terms used to get to the website, in addition to search terms used in the site’s search engine;
The dates and times users access the site;
The type of device used to access the site;
How often users visit the site;
The pages users visit within site; and
The links made to other websites through this site.
Information is not about your personal identity
The information is NOT identifiable by a person and is only used cumulatively for analytical purposes to help make Air Sports Net more user friendly. Google Analytics plants a persistent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit it, but no one but Google can use it. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.
Security
For site security purposes, the servers housing Air Sports Net use programs to monitor network traffic. Anyone using this site consents to monitoring their use by these programs and the analysis of traffic to recognize possible security breaches.
Information you knowingly provide
If you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information through a contact form, we will collect such information during your visit to Air Sports Net website. Examples of personally identifiable information may include:
Your name;
An email address if you are communicating to us through email;
The IP address of the computer where contact was initiated;
Other information volunteered, such as comments, questions, and suggestions about our website.
The information collected is not limited to text and may include audio, video, and other graphic formats you send us. Information is retained and used under existing laws, rules, regulations, and other policies.
Public Disclosure
As a general practice, we will not reveal any personally identifiable information collected online unless requested by law enforcement agencies.
7 Day Weather Forecast
National Weather MapsCurrent Temperature Map
Current Barometric Pressure Map
Current Dew Points Map
Current Relative Humidity Map
Current Visibility Map
Current Weather Map
Current Wind Direction Map
Popular Categories
Videos132Competition and Events103Skydiving News89Paragliding News56Hang Gliding News49Must See Videos48Skydiving Videos46Record Breaking News36Video of the Week32Base Jumping Videos27Paragliding Videos23Ultralight News22Science and Technology22Out of the ordinary22Hang Gliding Videos21
© Air Sports Net - 1999 to infinity and beyond!
Visitors Since 1999
